1884_05-23_Seymour-Record

The May 23, 1884 issue of the Seymour Record, records a bit of history which may be mis-interpreted by present-day readers. While it lists Oxford's statistics for 1819, this was prior to the 1859 incorporation of the Town of Seymour. So, the statistics listed are from what is now Oxford and parts of what is now Seymour. The public inn would have been the Oxford Hotel and the Congregational Church would have the parish now called the Oxford United Church of Christ, Congregational. The three historic items are listed below:

"The population of the town of Oxford in 1810 was 1,445."

"In 1816 the grand list amounted to $35,000."

"In 1819 the manufacturing establishments of the town of Oxford were thus enumerated: one woolen factory, three limekilns, one large hat factory, two fulling mills and clothiers' works, three carding machines for customers, three grain mills and six tanneries. There were three stores and one public inn. There were about 200 electors or freemen, one company of militia, 220 dwelling houses, one Congregational ecclesiastical society, two Episcopal and one Methodist; thirteen school districts, one clergyman, one physician, and one attorney."

The paper also include the Oxford news of 1884, as follows:

OXFORD.

Mrs. Foly, from Bridgeport, is visiting her parents.

Rev. Mr. Mohr of the Congregational church came to town with his family last week.

Nelson Botsford and wife of New York were guests at the Oxford House over Sunday.

Mrs. E. J. Perry has been on the sick list for several weeks. She is attended by Dr. Shove.

H. E. Tomlinson is delegate from Zoar Bridge M. E. Church to the Sunday School convention at Waterbury.

Julius Morris caught a turtle in the Eight Mile Brook which weighed twenty-one pounds. It is astonishing that it escaped the boys so long.

Rev. Mr. Bailey will preach a sermon in St. Peter's church next Sunday afternoon appropriate to memorial season. There will be no service in the morning, but Sunday school at the usual hour.

Last Saturday Orrin Tucker went to the aid of his dog, which was barking in the distance, and found he had three coons at bay, all of which were soon captured, the largest weighing over 16 pounds.

The centre school closed last week Thursday, and on Friday evening Mr. Fred Bailey and scholars gave a pleasant entertainment, consisting of singing, reading, recitations, dialogues and tableaus.

The county commissioners were called here to adjudicate in regard to the trees cut by the telegraph men along the highway near the river, but the matter was settled by the telegraph company paying Mr. Lum for the trees.

