1882_11-10_Seymour-Record

OXFORD.

Mrs. Charles Clark, a former resident, has been visiting here for a few days.

J. H. Hawley, who went from this place to Hawleyville a few years since, has returned in feeble health.

Chas. L. Curtiss commenced the winter term of school in the 8th district last Monday.

The election passed off quietly and with quite a full vote. Orlando C. Osborn, democrat, was elected representative by 44 majority, and Lewis Barnes judge of probate by 51 majority.

Smith C. Wheeler has moved to his new home in the 10th district.

Smith C. Wheeler, "the butcher," is to peddle on Mondays & Fridays, through the winter at least, and will peddle going up instead of down.

SOUTHFORD.

Erastus Burr and son had the misfortune to find one of their oxen dead last Monday morning. They used it last Saturday and it appeared as well as usual, then turned it out to pasture at night and did not see it till Monday, when they found it dead. It was thought to have died with a cattle disease which affects the lungs.

The school on Hull's Hill commenced its winter term last Monday, Charles Curtiss of Oxford, teacher.

Russel Fox is doing quite a business in getting out spokes and will purchase hickory timber. He is boardiug at the house of Erastus Burr.

SCANS:
http://www.oxfordpast.com/Seymour-record/1882/1982_11-10_Seymour-Record/SCAN1382.JPG
http://www.oxfordpast.com/Seymour-record/1882/1982_11-10_Seymour-Record/SCAN1383.jpg
