1884_08-01_Seymour-Record

OXFORD.

The remains of Miss Lucy Smith of Ansonia were brought to Quaker Farms on Monday for interment.

Mr. and Mrs. R. B. Limburner have been on a visit to Rev. F. E. Snow at South Windsor for the past week.

Mrs. B. I. Davis of Owego, N. Y., is making her annual visit to Connecticut and at present is with Mr. and Mrs. Burritt Davis of this place.

St. Peter's church Sunday school and all others who may choose to go will picnic at Wallace's grove, Quassapaug, on Thursday of next week.