1884-03-07_Seymour-Record

OXFORD.
  The storm of last week Thursday was followed by a cold wind and notwithstanding the snow was damp it yielded and on Friday morning commenced to drift on the hills and continued fearfully throughout the day, making the Chestnut-tree hill road, Riggs street and Christian street impassable. Mr. Wakelee, the new butcher, while attempting to go over his route on the former road struck a drift before he saw it, the snow was so blinding, and was capsized. 
  On Saturday the residents of the drifted sections were busy all day shoveling out, and then the streets were hardly passable so that considerable of the work was continued on Sunday. There has been no drifting of such proportions in many years, in fact one gentleman says that he never saw such drifts as those are on Christian street.
  Rev. Mr. Bailey resumed his discourses on the Ten Commandments last Sunday taking up the sixth "Thou shalt not kill," which he handled in a very interesting manner.
  The Ladies' Society of St. Peter's church met at the rectory this week.
  Henry Lum, formerly of this place, died in Ripon, Wis., on the 3d inst., with cancerous affliction. 

QUAKER FARMS.
  Mr Dietz Woostor is on the sick list.
  Mrs. Bidwell has returned to her home.
  We receive the mail daily by seventeen volunteer carriers.
  Last Wednesday police from Birmingham traced burglars through this place.
  Our neighbor C. C. Ryder has improved his house by the addition of new blinds.
  Mr. A. E. Arnold, who lately moved to Bridgeport, paid us a flying visit last week.
  Last Sunday Mr. Bailey preached a good sermon from 7th chapter 2nd Corinthians, 1st verse.
  A valuable cow owned by Silas Hawkins has been sick quite a while and it is feared he will lose it.
  As Chas. Davis met a load of furniture the other day his horse shied into the ditch, freeing himself from the sleigh, and threw Mr. Davis out, but doing little damage. 