1882_04-27_Seymour-Record

Oxford.

There was a small but pleasant party at the hop at the Oxford House last Thursday evening.

Rev. Mr. & Mrs. Snow attended the installation of Rev. Mr. Billman at East Windsor on Wednesday.

The Ladies Society of St. Peter's Church will meet at the residence of Mrs. O. C. Osborn on Tuesday afternoon and evening of next week, May 4th.

J. G. Stevens of Monroe and S. C. Wheeler of Oxford are the commissioners appointed by the senate for Zoar Bridge; John Candee and Albert W.Lum of Oxford, and H. W. Peck of Woodbridge, commissioners for Oxford turnpike.

The people of St. Peters parish, Oxford, Conn., recognizing the fact that the present welfare of their parish is largely due to the lively interest taken, and active work done therein by the Rev. H. G. Widdemer, and wishing to place on record their thankful appreciation of his self-denial and unrequited services of love among them while without a rector, have adopted, through a special committee appointed at the annual meeting, the following minute:

Resolved, That this parish is under great obligations to Mr. Widdemer for his generous help and willing services rendered during the past three years, as no call for ministrations has gone unheeded by him ; no request for help has been denied;

Resolved, That, in view of these facts, the parish desires to convey to him its hearty and sincere thanks for the same; and, as he is now called to another field of labor, to wish him a hearty God speed in the great vineyard of the master, where he so faithfully serves.

Committee
	WILLIAM E. POTWINE,
	LEWIS BARNES
	ELIJAH B. TREAT
