1892_05-11_Seymour Record

Great Hill.
" Twas Thursday evening, May the fourth. 
We gathered at the farmhouse hearth; 
" Twas not where lived little Jack Horner," But 'twas the big house on the corner.

An every day man, no rara avis,
Was our host, the genial Marcus Davis.
Xot all at once, but in time the guests came,
Bringing baskets of goodies, of Great Hill fame.

The silver haired sire and the gay, sportive maid. 
The dignified yeomen and the matrons staid. John Fanning, whose eyesight is fading away. And generous Maria who savetl her hay.

Young friends from Shelton, good brother Sherman, 
Who thrives out there mid the dews of Hermon, A poet from Biverside, sure as I Tolles you. And Mrs. Jones from Gotham, et ceteru.

The table was trimmed with running pine, 
A plate of pond lillies from the Bhine, 
With cake and pie and goodies plenty, 
Which were attacked at seven-twenty:

Then after supper some one saw— 
And surely 'twas against the law, 
An album which he thought he'd read, 
And said to make them laugh was need.

To this of course we'd no objection, 
Provided he took no collection. 
Mid lines of sentiment and affection, 
He read to them this choice (?) selection.

At midnight on the poultey roost,
A farm on Great Hill's highest boost.
The Turkey dreamed of the hour,
When in the grease he should be sizling,
Stuffed with bread crumbs and with flour ;
In dreams he heard the last faint squak
Of turkeys dying round him,
In dreams he heard old Jerry shout:
"Strike 'till not another pullet flies,
"Strike for roast turkey and chicken pies,
"And lots of feathers too."
He fought like a brave man long and well,
He piled that ground with goblers slain,
He conquered, but the turkeys fell,
Bleeding at every vein.

The leaves were graced with flowers and vines. And only sharp eyes saw the lines, 
They said he dreamed them when he'd had 
Late supper off a turk or shad.

The album's owner wished he wouldn't, 
And one old lady said he shouldn't, 
Who wrote the page was sure he couldn't, 
Have found in it such liues discordant.

And so with jests the evening passed, 
Of course it could not always last, 
And from the group so merry hearted, 
We regretfully departed.

And when some eve again they meet, 
I thence will turn my willing feet, 
For there's a way where there's a will 
To merry gatherings on Great Hill.

OXFORD

C. B. Perry and Frank Curtiss are painting the residence of Mrs. R. B. Limburner.

Joel White is making a long needed improvement around his residence viz: a new fense.

Rev. Mr. Snow will nold service next Sunday at 8.80. pm at five mile hill school house.

Rev. Mr. Gardener of Naugatuck will visit St. Peters Church next Sunday at 2:30 pm for the purpose of administering baptisn and the communion.