         1884_07-18_Seymour-Record

QUAKER FARMS.

Mrs. C. C. Ryder has been making a short visit at the home of her mother in Woodmont.

Mrs. George Skidmore had the misfortune to fall one night last week and hurt her hip quite badly. In coming down stairs, thinking she had reached the bottom, she stepped off three stairs and fell.

A pear tree standing in the back yard of one of our neighbors was in blossom the first of this month. It never having blossomed before, and being eight or ten years old, it seemed a more curious freak of nature.

Mrs. H. E. Bidwell is improving as fast as can possibly be expected and with the best of care, by an excellent nurse, will undoubtedly soon be up again. The stone in memory of her late husband was placed in position last week. It is from the marble works in Bridgeport.

The late frequent rains have started vegetation, so that the farmers show satisfaction in the thought that their labor has not been in vain. The dampness combined with the cool nights produces an abundance of malaria.

SOUTHFORD.

Mrs. Erastus Burr has been on the sick list for some time. It is hoped she will improve and be about again.

Mrs. Horace Oatman died last Thursday at the advanced age of 79 years. She was much respected and will be greatly missed, not only in the family but in the community. She leaves an aged husband and two sons to mourn her loss. Her funeral was largely attended from her late place of residence last Sunday afternoon, Rev. Mr. Bailey officiating. A large circle of friends and relatives followed her remains to the grave in Southford cemetery.