1882_02-09_Seymour-Record

Today's Old News is from the Feb. 9, 1882 issue of the Seymour Record. The news of the day relates to the large snow storm which closed the churches on Sunday. The Quaker Farms news credits the local man who used teams and a large roller to open the roads. Instead of plowing snow to the sides, the custom was to run a heavy roller over it, to pack the snow, making it ideal for sleighing.

Today's old photo is of the Oxford Congregational Church in snow shows the building before the addition of the educational building, apparently taken around the 1930's.


OXFORD
The project of uniting Christ Church and St. Peter's under one rector is again being agitated.

Rev. Mr. Snow expects to hold services at Christian street next Sunday at 3:30 p.m.

The Bishop of the diocese will visit St. Peter's Church and administer the rite of confirmation next Sunday. Services to commence about 2 p.m.

One of the pleasantest occasions of the dancing season is anticipated at the Calico Ball, at the Oxford House on Thursday evening, Feb. 16th.

C. B. Perry is taking a rest from his studies on account of ill health.

On account of the storm of Saturday there was no service in either church last Sunday.

Miss Mary E. Hubbell closed the winter term of the 3rd district school last week.

Prof. Dibble's entertainment last Monday evening was as well attended as could have been expected, considering the traveling.

A sleigh party of about twenty from Birmingham visited the Oxford House, last Friday evening.

A party made up from Southford, Southbury, Quakers Farm and this place went on a sleigh ride to Newtown on Wednesday. The programme was to have a dance and supper at the Central House. At this writing we have received no tidings but no doubt a pleasant time was had.

QUAKER FARMS  

On account of the storm on Saturday and the blockade of snow the church was not opened for service on Sunday,

Our energetic neighbor, S. C. Hubbell, was out with teams and a large roller breaking the roads.

Miss Sarah Patterson, aged 27 years, daughter of Simeon Patterson, formerly of this place, died at Birmingham and was brought here and buried on Monday last.

Mrs. Horace Hinman, who has been quite sick for some time, is slowly improving.
0
SOUTHFORD

Harriet L., wife of Henry Curtiss, a much esteemed lady of this place, died on Thursday morning, Feb. 2nd, at the age of 62 years. She leaves a husband to mourn her loss. The funeral services were held in the Congregational church in Southbury last Saturday afternoon, Rev. Mr. Snow of Oxford officiating, assisted by Rev. Mr. Miller.

There was another large party and social dance at Henry S. Wheeler's Hall Friday evening, Feb. 3rd. Bliss' band of Monroe furnished music as usual.

 