1881_07-07_Seymour-Record

OXFORD

Rev. S. R. Bailey will officiate in St. Peter's church next Sunday.

The rain interfered somewhat with the success of the Congregatipual festival at the town hall.

The funeral of Mrs. Lucinda M. Sanford was attended on Thursday, interment at Bethany, Rev. S. R. Bailey officiating.

Rev. Mr Miller, of Southbury will occupy the pulpit of the Congregational church next Sabbath in exchange with Rev. Mr. Snow.

A goodly number of both denominations called on Rev. Mr. Potwine on Sunday evening to bid him God speed in the new field he has chosen.

Young America commenced celebrating the 4th before the 3d had hardly passed. Some of the young people spent the day at Quassapaug and others at High Rock.

The Mutual Union Telegraph Co., having fully investigated the reports which caused the discharge of John McCune, operator at this place, find that he has been falsely represented and has reinstated him. His return is heartily welcomed by the people here. 

ZOAR BRIDGE.

A strawberry and ice cream festival was held in a tent in front of our little church on Wednesday evening, June 28th, for the benefit of the society. There  was quite a gathering and it

MISC.:

The recent boast that 0. M. Crosby of Danbury has the largest peach orchard in New England(l,600), is out done by the Norwalk Gazette, which says that John E. Scofield of Hunting Ridge, has 2,000 peach trees and a neighbor has 1,000 more, the latter set out this spring. Peach raising seems not to be considered the poor business it formerly was in Connecticut.

SCANS:


http://www.oxfordpast.com/Seymour-record/1882/1982_07-07_Seymour-Record/SCAN1318.JPG

http://www.oxfordpast.com/Seymour-record/1882/1982_07-07_Seymour-Record/SCAN1319.JPG

http://www.oxfordpast.com/Seymour-record/1882/1982_07-07_Seymour-Record/SCAN1320.JPG