The Seymour Record
Friday, May 16, 1884.

OXFORD.
EARLY   HISTORY   OF THE
CONGREGATIONAL CHURCH.
-No. 40.-

1780.
March 19th, Jared Osborn & Freelove Ame his wife owned ye covenant.

March 19th, Justus Caude owned his covenant.

April 2d, Isaac Chatfield & Sarah his.wife owned ye covenant. 

July 16, James Riggs & Sarah his wife ownd ye covenant. 

July 16, Joseph Bassit & Molly his wife ownd ye covenant.

1781.

April 1, Eli Chatfield, & Lois his Wife ownd ye covenant.

1787.

April 8, Timothy Johnson, Jnr Renewd his covenant. 

April 22, Lieut. Naboth Osborn & Susie his Wife renewed their covenant. 

April 22, Samuel Buckingham & Ruth bis Wife renewed their covenant. 

July 15, Samll Tucker, Jnr, & Silence his Wife renewd their covenant. 

Septr 30, Sarah, wife of Jerh Mather Kelly, renewd her covenant.

1788.

July 20, Isaac Brizcho & Mary his wife renewed their covenant. 

	Job Cande & Sarah his wife Renewd their covenant.

1790.

June 20, Abel Waters & Ruth his Wife renewd their covenant. 

July 25, Hezekiah Hine & Hannah his Wife renewd their covenant. 

July 25, David Smith, Jnr, & Abilena his Wife renewd their covenant. 

August 15, Truman Stodard & Sarah his wife renewd their covenant. 

Decr 5, Roger Perkins & Betsey his Wife renewed their covenant.

1791.

April 10, Amos Fox and Jemima his Wife renewed their covenant. 

1792.

April 23d, William Lewis Jnr & Sarah his wife renewed their Covenant. 

April 22d, Nathll Buckingham Jnr & Silena his wife renewed ye Covenant. 

May 6th, Lucy Tucker Renewed her Covenant. 

May 13th, Daniel Fox & Elizabeth his Wife Renewd their Covenant. 

Novr 4th, Joel Perry & Betty his Wife renewed their Covenant. 

1793.

Janr 27th, Lewis Blackman renewed his Covenant.

May 12th, Molly Bristoll renewed her Covenant. 

June 2d, Philo R. Bristol & Nabby his Wife Renewed their Covenant. 

1794.

Aug. 24th, Samuel Riggs and Charry his wife renewed their Covenant.

Aug. 24, Philo Beecher & Mary his Wife renewed their Covenant.

Septr 21st, John Riggs 3d & Mary his Wife Renewed their Covenant. 

Sept. 21, Wm Morriss & Elizabeth his wife Renewed their Covenant. 

Septr 28th, Daniel Smith & Lucy his wife Renewed their Covenant. 

Septr 28th, Daniel Riggs Renewed his Covenant. 

1796.

Janr 17th, Enoch Bristoll & and Sarah Wife renewed their Covenant. 

Decr 11th, Capt. Asahel Hide & Mary Dorman Leavenworth [his wife]
Chester Smith & Kezia his wife 
Philomon Hinman & Polly his Wife 
Renewed their Covenant. 

1797

Octr 15, Walker Wilmot & MilleCent renewed their Covenant. 
Ethiel Lounsbury & Betsey his wife renewed their Covnt.
Caleb Tomlinson & Nabby his wife wife renewed their Coveut. 

Novm 26, Joseph Perkins & Sarah his wife renewed their covnt.

1798

May 27th, Cyrus Caude & Rebekah his Wife Renewd their Covenant.

Septm 9, Lemuel Beardsey & Mercy his wife Renewed their Covenant. 

1799
October 13, Miles Loveland & Anne his wife Renewed their Covenant. 

1800

Septr 21, Joseph Riggs & Lyddia his wife renewed their Covenant.

Septmr 21, John Fairchild & Mary his wife renewed their Covenant.

Septmrr 21, David Beecher & Polly his wife renewd their Covenant.


REMOVALS, &c.

April 27th, 1764, Abigail the wife of Aaron Sperry Dismissed from this Chh & Recommended to the Chh at Gr. Barrington.

April 3d, 1765, Peter Negro Dismissed & Reccomended to the Chh at Amity.

July 18th, Samuel Chatfield and Joannah his wife Dismissed from this Church & Recomended to the Church at Waterbury.

Decr lst, Ebenezer Blackman & Margett his wife dismissed from this Church & Recomended to the Church at Nobletown.

Jane 7th, 1767, Lois the wife of Amos Camp Jnr Dismissed from this Church and Recomended to the Church at New Milford.

June 5th, Moses Cande & Sarah his Wife renewd their Covenant. 

July 3d, Medad Candee & Betty his Wife renewd their Covenaut. 

August 7th, Nehemiah Durand & Ruth his Wife Renewd their Covenant. 

Septr 18th, Truman Bristol & Polly his Wife renewed their Covenant. 

Septr, 18, John Buckingham & Lucy his Wife renewd their Covenant. 

March 25, 1770, Joel Northrop Dismissed from this Chh & Recomended to the Chh at Newbury.

June 5th, 1770, Eleazar Wooster & Deborah his Wife Recomended to the Church of Christ at Goshen.

June 5th, 1770, Elizabeth the wife of John Smith Recomended to the Church of Christ at Goshen.

Novr 1770, Eunice Wife to David Mansfield Recomended to the Church at Northbury.

May 3d, 1772, David Graves & Hannah his wife Recomended to the Chh in Southbury.

June 7th, Samuel Woodruffe and Ann his wife Recommended to the Chh in Litchfield South Farm.

July 26th, Reuben Hale Recommended to the Chh at Hartland.

Janr 17th, 1773, Nathan Fairchild & Lois his Wife Recomended to the Chh at Ripton.

May 16th, Gershom Lake & Zerviah his wife Dismissed from this Church & Recomended to the Chh of Christ where God in his Providence may call ym.

Septr 5th, John Holbrook and Eunice his Wife Recomended to the Church in Southbury.

1774, May 30th, Jeremiah Riggs and Anne his wife, recommended to the Church at Litchfield South Farms.

1775, Febr 26th, Thomas Ufford and Mable his wife dismissed from this Church and recomended to the Church of Christ where God in his providence may call them.

1776, Novr 24th, Isaac Trowbridge & Judith his wife dismissed from the watch & care of this Chu & Recomended to the Chh at Litchfield, by vote of the Chh.

Novr 24th, voted that James Pangborn & Prudence his wife be dismissed from the Chh & Recomended to the Church Sharon for the Privilidge of Baptism of of Children.

1781, June 10th, voted, That Capt Daniel Chatfield & Prudence his wife be dismissed from this Chh and be Recomended to the Chh in Waterbury for the Privilidges of Special Ordinances.

1782, Feb. 10th, Voted that Joseph Washborn & his wife be recommended to the Chh in part of Spencertown for the Privilidge of Baptism of their Children.

1783, July 13th, Voted that Lois the wife of Reuben Perkins be Recomended to the Church at West britain for the Privilidges of Special Ordinances.

1783, Octr 12th, Voted, that Sarah Downs be Recomended to the Church at Sandersfield for the Privilidge of Special Ordinances.

Novr 9th, Voted that Joseph Osborn Jnr and Rebekah his wife be Recomended to the Chh at Westbritain for the Privilidge of Special Ordinances.

1786, Septr 24th, Voted that Tabitha Wife of Mr Reuben Tucker be recomended by Letter to the first Chh in Derby for the Privilidge of Special Ordinances.

Novr 1st, 1789, Voted that Mary the Wife of Thomas Knowles be recomended to Communion in the Church at Lottania.

May 8th, 1791, Voted that Gad Bristoll Jnr be recomended to Communion in the Church at Southbury.

July 28th, 1793, Voted that Nehemiah Cande and Content his wife (being moved from us into the New Settlements) be recomended to any Church where God in his Providence may call them.

May 3d, 1795, Voted the Eleazar Wooster and Deborah his wife be recomended to the Pastor & Chh of Bethlehem for Gospel Ordinances.

May 1st, 1796, Voted that John Botsford and Rachel his wife be Recomended to the Church in Salisbury.

Janr 3d, 1797, Voted that David Cande be Recomended to the Pastor & Chh at Harrington as having Renewd his Covenant and of a good moral character.

Test.  D. Brownson, Pastor.

May 16th, 1802, Voted that Anne the wife of Abner Bradley be Recomended to the Chh in Woodbridge.

Test. D. Brownson, Pastor.




