1884_06-20_Seymour-Record


GREAT HILL.
Tbe ladies of the Great Hill Church will hold a strawberry and ice cream festival in a large tent near the church on Thursday evening the 26th. Seymour friends are specially invited.

The Sunday school will meet next Sunday at 12 o'clock instead of the usual hour. A "love feast" service is to be held at 1:30, followed at 2:30 by preaching by the presiding elder, Rev. W. H. Wardell. The quarterly conference will meet at the close of the service.


OXFORD.

C. B. Ferry arrived home last Saturday evening. 

The Guild meetings are postponed till August.

E. N. Tucker moved his picture gallery to Seymour on Monday.

Miss Cora Bailey, organist of St. Peter's church, is taking a vacation in New York and elsewhere.

There was a misunderstanding and no little disappointment as to Rev. Mr. Potwine being at St. Peter's last Sunday. It was Rev. Mr. Bailey of Waterbury that he was to assist. Rev. Mr. Potwiue however made a flying visit here on Tuesday and promised to be with us some Sunday in July.