1884_06-20_Seymour-Record

Today's "Old News" from the June 20, 1884 issue of the Seymour Record includes notice of a strawberry and ice cream festival at Great Hill Church.  Today's Old Photo is from the late Howard Belinsky, of the Oxford Athletic Club baseball team. 

Today's new image is notice of the Historical Society's plans for the annual peach festival at the same church. Since the church now has a fellowship hall, there will be no need for a tent. The annual festival will feature photos from our local schools and local sports teams. Persons who have photos of local sports teams, from any time in the past are asked to contact photos@oxford-historical-society.org to make arrangements for the photos to be scanned and duplicated.

GREAT HILL.
Tbe ladies of the Great Hill Church will hold a strawberry and ice cream festival in a large tent near the church on Thursday evening the 26th. Seymour friends are specially invited.

The Sunday school will meet next Sunday at 12 o'clock instead of the usual hour. A "love feast" service is to be held at 1:30, followed at 2:30 by preaching by the presiding elder, Rev. W. H. Wardell. The quarterly conference will meet at the close of the service.


OXFORD.

C. B. Ferry arrived home last Saturday evening. 

The Guild meetings are postponed till August.

E. N. Tucker moved his picture gallery to Seymour on Monday.

Miss Cora Bailey, organist of St. Peter's church, is taking a vacation in New York and elsewhere.

There was a misunderstanding and no little disappointment as to Rev. Mr. Potwine being at St. Peter's last Sunday. It was Rev. Mr. Bailey of Waterbury that he was to assist. Rev. Mr. Potwiue however made a flying visit here on Tuesday and promised to be with us some Sunday in July.