1884_06-07_Seymour-Record

OXFORD.

The Ladies' Society of St. Peter's church will meet with Mrs. F. C. Candee on Thursday of next week.

Rev. Mr. Bailey started on Monday to meet Mrs. Bailey on her way from Vineland, N. J., with their team.

Next Sunday being St. Peter's day the services in St. Peter's church will be appropriate for the occasion. There will be services all day.

Dr. E. B. Fairchild has again been obliged to give up the dentistry business for a while at least, on account of his health. Mrs. Fairchild, who has been visiting in the West for sometime, returned on Monday.

During the shower on Wednesday a bolt of lightning entered Joel Perry's house, shattering a window casing and the plastering. No one happened to be in the room at the time, only Ben Butler, who made a black streak to the center covered with plastering.