1884_05-15_Seymour-Record

OXFORD.
Mrs. L. L. Leek was on a visit to her son, F. A. Leek over Sunday.

A call for a caucus will be found in another column.

Perry Bros, have greatly improved the exterior of Mrs. P. P. Warner's residence by a liberal application with the brush.

Rev. Mr. Bailey and family have moved to the west side and occupy the John Smith place at Five Mile Hill.

Mrs. George Fairchild of Bridgeport, with her two daughters and son, are spending a few days in town.

The Guild meetings have been resumed and the annual meeting was held and well attended at the residence of W. W. Hughes on Wednesday evening, the 6th. The next meeting will be held at the residence of Mrs. Elisha Wheeler, in Southford, on Saturday of this week.

The flag which waved in honor of the successful candidates four years ago has again been thrown to the breeze, suspended from the same pole and old elm in front of the post office, and also very appropriately carries the name of him, James G. Blaine, who as was thought by the lamented Garfield good enough to occupy the most important position within the gift of the Executive of the nation, and who will according to indications be called even higher in November by an unmistakable vote of the people.

The unfavorable weather last week Thursday interfered greatly with the attendance and enjoyableness of St. Peter's church picnic at Quassapaug. There were however sixty or more present and while boating and all out door sports were dampened, the company enjoyed themselves quite well. The tables, which were provided by Mr. Wallace in the building, were abundantly laden and dinner and supper was quite as heartily enjoyed as if all had been sunshine without. A number who did not go on this day and some who did went up on Friday and had a pleasant time. In fact some went again on Saturday, but the third trip was in search of a chain and locket which was lost on the 2d day and which they were fortunate to find in the sand near the lake.

The Congregational society had a good day for their picnic on Wednesday of this week. There was a large attendance and it goes without saying they had a very pleasant time. Rev. Mr. Snow arrived just in season on his vacation visit to enjoy this gathering of his former parishoners and friends. 

HULL'S HILL.

Dog days has furnished rather poor hay weather during the past two weeks.

Mrs. Ira Skeels, who has been sick with dropsy complaint during the past six months, is very low. It is feared she will not recover. Dr. Barnes of Oxford attends her.

At the annual school meeting held at the school house in this place last Saturday evening Eras Burr was elected committee and Amos T.White was re-elected clerk for the coming year. The district contemplate repairing their schoo1 house this fall.

The base ball fever is raging as usual. The Poverty nine of Southbury came to this place last Saturday and played with the Riverside nine. The contest continued till nearly dark when the Poverty nine started for home defeated but not cast down, hoping for better luck next time.