1899_07-13_Seymour-Record

GREAT HILL.

Mr. E. T. Bice of Seymour is expected to preach for us next Sabbath morning. There will be no service in the evening.

The church was struck by lightning Saturday. One of the timbers of the spire was splintered, though the top of the spire and the bell seem not to have been touched. The northwest corner of the church was most damaged, both the cornice and the corner post being splintered and the clapboards torn off. The plaster was somewhat broken. The ground was thickly strewed with boards and splinters. The church was insured but whether this damage by lightning was covered is not yet ascertained.

There is quite a historical sketch of this church in the "Annals of the Seymour M. E. Church," second edition, published last year at the Record office.

Miss Nancy Smith is staying with her aunt, Mrs. Coleman.

Rev. Mr. Abbott administered the communion at the service Sunday morning.

Mrs. Marcus Davis has been ill for some days, also Arthur Pruden Coleman, but both are convalescing.

Miss Blanche Wells is spending some time in Middlefield and expects to visit in West Haven and New Haven.

Abbie Moshier is spending a part of her vacation with her aunt, Mrs. E. J. Powe, of 926 Main street, Bridgeport.

Henry Seymour of Great Hill will move his family to the home of his parents, at Randolph, Orange Co., Vt., the last of next week. Mr. Seymour has been spending some days there with his mother, who has been very sick, but will now remain in this vicinity for a month.

OXFORD.

Edward Brossman of Stafford Springs has been visiting with Dr. Melbourne, at the Center, for a few days.

The pleasant shower of Wednesday evening was very acceptable as it had become very dusty on the roads again.

Wilbur Alling and wife of Norwich spent Sunday and Monday with his parents, Mr. and Mrs. E. J. Alling, on Christian street.

Miss Florence James of Seymour spent Sunday as a guest of Mrs. Sherman Sanford, who is convalescing from an illness of about a week.

Rev. E. T. Matthison of Ansonia conducted services in St. Peter's church last Sunday as Rev. Mr. Woodford was unwell. The communion was celebrated.

The heavy rains of Saturday while of great benefit to wells and streams and all crops, was also a source of considerable damage to roads in different parts of town.

W. H. S. Barnes is spending one week of his vacation from his duties at the grocery and provision store of Mr. Hurlburt in New Haven at his home in the Center and is helping his father at haying.

Frank Munn of New Haven came up on his wheel and spent Sunday with his mother, Mrs Marcus Munn, who is stopping with Mr. and Mrs. W. W. Hughes at their pleasant home in the Center.

William W. Fairchild and wife with Miss Minnie Wuterich of Tracy, near Meriden, spent Sunday as guests of Mrs. K. N. Davis, aunt of Mr. Fairchild. Miss Wuterich remains for a visit of a few weeks with friends.

David M. Fairchild, who has been staying with his daughters in St. Paul, Minn., has returned to his home in Danbury and with his son Charles G. Fairchild, and wife, is visiting with his sister, Mrs. K. M. Davis, in this place.

A lawn party is to be given by the Young People's society and the Christian Endeavor society on the large lawn of the pleasant home of Clinton E. Russell on Christian street the last week of this month. The date and further details will be given next week.

On Wednesday of last week one Charles Murphy, a sewing machine agent from Naugatuck, was tried before Justice R. G. Robinson for fraud in regard to the repairing of an old machine for Mrs. Wales Chatfield, and for abusive language. His fine and costs amounted to about $16, which he paid.

Next Sunday forenoon Rev. Mr. Biller, who has been a missionary for a number of years among the Indians ot the Indian Territory, is expected to be at St. Peter's church with Rev. W. A. Woodford. He is said to be a speaker of more than the average ability and his address on the subject of Indian missions will undoubtedly be both interesting and instructive.


QUAKER FARMS.

Two more teachers are needed in the mission Sundayschool at the hall.

Miss Clara Hawkins has been recently visiting relatives in Meriden.

Miss Matilda Avery of Colchester has been spending a week with Miss Mabel Lum.

Rev. Mr. Mathison of Ansonia conducted service at the church Sunday afternoon, on account of the illness of Rev. Mr. Woodford, who it is expected will be able to officiate as usual next Sunday. Rev. Mr. Billar, who has done missionary work among the Indians of Indian Territory, will also be present next Sunday and will speak in the interests of the work.

SOUTHFORD.

All welcome the showers, the rain was so much needed for the growing  crops and rowen.

Mr. and Mrs. Charles R. Edwards were entertained at the home of G. E Garlick over Sunday. 

Henry Curtiss had the misfortune to have his foot hurt quite badly by being stepped on by his horse.

Messrs. William Davis & Son have had new windows put in their store. B. C. Pope doing the work.

John Lyman of New York has been visiting at Hurley E. Warner's. He is a son of the late Dr. Sidney Lyman of New Preston.

Sherman Sanford is furnishing telephone poles for the new line, some of them being forty feet long. The poles are cut on the piece of timber he purchased of Dwight M. Atwood.

David Smith, night watchman at the papermill, thought he would take a day off and visit his children in Oakville, so started Saturday morning on his wheel, but was obliged to return on account of the heavy rain.

Amicus.