 The Seymour Record.

The Record was established in 1871, previous to which time there was no paper published in any of the towns between Derby and Waterbury. It was at first a small eight page sheet, changing in September, 1886, to a six column quarto.

The Record has been conducted as a local family paper, giving the greatest prominence to matters of interest to the people of Seymour and adjoining towns, and has from time to time contained engravings of public buildings, factories and prominent people of the place, with occasional historical sketches, both by the editor and by people of Seymour and neighboring towns who have contributed valuable articles on the early history of their several communities, so that the files of the Record are a mine of information both in regard to current events and early local history.
